I guess I'm dating Senpai now.
Even after everything,
it still seems unreal.
My feet feel like they're floating in air.
You hungry?
Want something before we go?
Uh... I'll leave that to you.
Then let's get the roasted corn.
We could get the potatoes
with the butter on top, too.
I wonder if he's talking
about the Jagabutter?
He's certainly used to
this stuff, isn't he...
Even though my heart's been
pounding hard this whole time.
I wonder how long you hold hands for?
My palms are sweaty, and I wonder if this
makes it harder for him to walk...
Oh! Isn't that the grilled corn?
Let's really take a look
around while we're here!
What do you normally eat
at festivals, Senpai?
I eat baby castellas, candy
apples, choco bananas...
Okay. Let's go then.
Oh gosh, it's all the sweet stuff...
All right, let's start heading back.
It'll be dangerous if we get separated.
B-But my hands are sweaty.
Like I care about that.
And, I'm still sort of embarrassed to...
Then you better get used to it.
I dunno what to do otherwise.
Okay.
We're really "boyfriend"
and "girlfriend," huh...
He looked so different
from his usual self.
Yoi! Please clean up your yukata. Yoi?
Someday, we'll be doing that
sort of thing, too, won't we?
Huh?
Now that it's official, how
should I behave at school?
Y'know what? I got a girlfriend.
My honey!
Yoi-chan!
O-Oh, gosh, I can see it now!
Congrats!
Thank you very much.
I figured that's what happened afterwards!
Must be real nice.
Your first boyfriend!
You up on cloud nine?!
Um, are you guys
free at lunch today?
Don't think I've ever heard you
hum a tune before, Ichi.
Hmm? Really?
Sheesh, must be nice to be so carefree.
The festival got super awkward
after you ran off, Ichi.
My b, my b.
It's just that, you see,
I started dating Yoi-chan.
What?
No way!
Way.
For real?! You didn't feed her
a line or anything?!
You didn't drug her, did you?!
Sentaro-kun.
Ow ow ow ow!
Good for you. Congrats.
Kuwa!
Wha? You pulled a wrestling move on me...
You have a new message.
Would you like to have lunch with
me in the old school building?
Um, three of you?
Is that not okay with you?
Well, it's okay if it's
every once in a while...
Like once a year.
Yay!
Thanks for having us!
Oh, shoot!
You guys...
Kinda happened on a whim.
Go away, shoo shoo.
Um, since you're here, you're
both welcome to join us.
What?
Seriously, what is this?
Are we having a meeting?
Now that we're officially dating,
I thought it would be good to properly
introduce each other's friends.
Oh, well, I suppose I could think of
it as two families meeting...
Oh, you're Tone-san, right?
Huh?
Wasn't the picture you drew in art class
the one they put up by the entrance?
Oh...
Seriously? What was the picture?
It was a sculpture-like thing.
Wow, that's amazing! Could you
show me one next time?!
I-I'm not that great, really...
She's blushing.
School
Motto
Steady progress towards your goal,
with sober and irreproachable conduct.
Anyways, I wanted to talk to you about
our future relationship plans.
Regarding future
relationship plans.
I thought it would be best for
everyone to be on the same page.
The most important point is
gradually revealing our relationship,
over the course of six months to a year,
to people outside the six who are here.
Then, just to be safe,
when walking home together, we should let
the other person know in advance
and walk three meters apart.
When walking side by side,
be sure to do it at least two
kilometers away from the school.
Regarding dates and other things...
Hold up. Stop, stop.
Um, we are dating, right?
Yes.
Then why do we have to hide it?
Because a lot of people
look up to you, Senpai.
And since we're both high school students,
-As a basic rule, plans should be discussed and
decided more than a week in advance.
-Avoid areas where the school staff can see us
together.
-Be mindful to behave appropriately and maintain
proper manners as a high school student.
(Avoid excessive physical contact.)
it's important to maintain a reasonable
distance and remain modest.
Yoi-chan is such a good girl.
Oh, something must have happened.
Did you do something to her?
Okay, okay, I'll read it later.
Hey! Not later, please read it now!
Besides, I have class duties today
so I can't walk home with you.
Okay.
Please answer properly.
Yesh, ma'am.
They're flirting.
Enunciate!
Yes, ma'am.
More properly!
Jeez, am I really the only
one thinking about the future?
Oh? Hey, what are the chances?
Huh? What are you doing?
What do you mean? I was waiting for you.
No way...
Yep, sorry, I was kidding.
I was actually called to
the office for detention.
But since I'm here, do you
wanna walk home together?
Huh? You in a bad mood?
Uh, hey...
How long do we have to...
Until we're more than two
kilometers away from the school.
Oh, yeah? Roger that.
Oh... And for a moment,
I was so happy, too.
And now it's "since I'm here."
Wait, wasn't I the one who
decided how things should be?
Regarding future
relationship plans.
Am I contradicting myself?
You mentioned detention.
Did you do something again?
Oh, yeah... this and that?
What do you mean "this and that?"
Well, it's like that thing, y'know?
What is "that thing"?
More like...
I was lying about that.
What? Why would you...
'Cause I wanted to be
alone with you, of course.
I'll have you know...
I'm already super infatuated with you.
I want you to be completely
infatuated with me!
Y'know... Don't make me say it, all right?
I see. Even just now, he...
I see.
Senpai!
Whoa!
What's goin' on?
Um, about the plan...
What do you say we reconsider it?
Y'know, Yoi-chan...
Just when I'm trying my best to be good,
you seriously go off and pull
stuff like that on me, don't you?
Huh? What do you mean? Pull what stuff?
Nah, it's all good now.
But seriously, please get used to
it as quickly as you can, okay?
There's no way people's feelings
go as planned, and yet...
I said I'll reconsider it, but I don't
know if I'll change anything yet.
Yep, yep.
Hey, what are ya gonna do about the
"two kilometers away from school" rule?
That's something that
needs to be considered.
Oh, can I buy ice cream
at the convenience store?
It's almost time for my first
summer break with a boyfriend.
Sure.
Oh, man.
I'm excited about summer break,
but the closing ceremony is
such a pain, don't ya think?
Calling everyone into the
gym in this heat is just ridiculous.
Right? At least put on the air
conditioner or something.
I know, right?
He's so cool!
Just as always.
Oh! Is that Ichimura-senpai?
Oh, you're right!
Oh! Yoi-chan, it's the Prince!
I know.
Kya!
He just waved at me, didn't he?!
There go the meaningless
arguments again...
To me, right?!
Well, that one packed quite a punch...
No! He was waving at me!
I see. So this is what a
sense of superiority feels like.
Something similar happened before.
I'm surprised at how my
feelings have changed.
Nasu Oyaji Curry
Yoi! You can clock out soon!
Oh, okay!
You have a new message.
Let me know when you're done with work.
Yo.
Thank you... for waiting.
Sorry for asking right
after work. Here you go.
You don't always have
to give me something...
Don't worry about it. Something
for making it to summer break.
Oh.
Mr. Papico Distributor.
It's good.
Do you have any plans for summer break?
Huh?
Well, y'know, vacation
with family and what not.
Oh, I mostly work.
I was also asked to tutor
my neighbor's child.
Wow, I can totally see that.
Do you have plans, Senpai?
Hmm? Oh, nothing in particular.
But I thought we could hang out together.
What?
Well, I am your boyfriend.
That's right...
Right...
But I kind of feel bad for asking
you to go out of your way.
I've been wondering. Why do you
have such low self-esteem?
Huh? Do I?
I thought it was normal.
It's super low.
It's not normal to say stuff like that.
You don't?
So, when are you free?
Let's see...
Monday through Friday I have work,
and I'll tutor on the weekends.
After my radio exercises,
I do have two hours.
Two hours? No way.
How about in the morn—
Mornings are reserved
for my studies.
Two hours.
Oh? I might have... these two days off?
Yoi-san.
San?
Please give me both of those days.
Sure, but was there something
you wanted to do?
Maybe something I want to do,
maybe somewhere I want to go...
How about a short trip to Kobe?
K-Kobe?!
Yes, Kobe.
B-But isn't it a bit far
to go for a day trip?
It's all right. We have a villa in Kobe.
I forgot this guy is rich.
You do mean a day trip, right?
Well, y'know.
It is summer break.
Denied.
We'd be in separate rooms, though?
That's not the problem!
Wha? But Kobe has a lot of delicious
Western confectionery stores...
There's cheesecake, Baumkuchen,
stuff with cream on top,
stuff with cream inside,
cheesecake and more!
I-I'll go, if I can bring my friends.
Wh-What is it now?
Nah, my bad, my bad.
Man, that was good.
Your determination wavers when
sweets are involved.
Okay. Then let's have fun
in Kobe as a group.
Oh, he's okay with it.
Well, it's getting late,
so I'll take you home.
Shark Park
Oh. I'm fine on my own.
No can do.
It's dangerous for a girl to be alone.
All right, let's go.
He's treating me
more and more like a girl...
Yoi-chan. Hold still...
Hmm?
There's a huge bug on your shoulder.
Hello.
Bye-bye.
Senpai...
Hmm?
You're okay with bugs?
I'm not good with them,
but I can touch them.
Y-You're so cool.
Huh?! What?
After everything, that's
what makes you think I'm cool?
I just can't deal with bugs at all...
I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean—
There's nothing wrong
being this close, y'know?
Let's stay like this for a while.
Wh-What are you saying?
We're in public!
It's fine, it's fine.
No one can see us in the dark.
No good?
You don't want to?
Maybe... just for five minutes.
Oh, Senpai's smell...
Until recently, I never thought
I'd be holding him like this.
Oh, shi—
No, that's not what I...
It was just on impulse.
Sorry, it wasn't intentional.
D-Dash
Ah, hey, Yoi-chan?!
Yoi-san! Yoi-sama!
Kobe?! I'll go, I'll go, I want to go!
But are you sure it's
okay for us to go, too?!
More like, I'd be bothered
if you didn't come.
Sorry for the short notice.
But still!
Even if you did have to bring us,
you didn't turn him down, Yoi-chan!
Well, it is summer break, after all...
Yippee!
That's good. That's good!
That's right!!
Let's go to Kobe and dress you up all
cute so Senpai's heart skips a beat!
But I don't really care what clothes—
Okay, let's go, let's go!
They look a bit like Senpai's.
I wonder... if he'll think it's cute?
I'm sorry I'm late!
The train had a delay.
I'm very sorry, Oji-kun.
Oh, no worries.
We're not that busy, so it's all right.
Oh? Did you get your ears pierced?
Huh?! Oh...
I forgot to take them off!
They're clip-ons. I just bought them.
They kind of look similar to the
ones that regular wears.
Y-You think so?!
It's a common design, and so...
Oh, I see.
I'll just put them in my pocket for now.
Well, I kinda wondered if the
two of you were dating or something.
Oh! I didn't mean anything...
Actually...
We are.
Yoi!
Ah! Coming!
What is it?
Are yukatas... something guys like?
My friend is planning to go to
the summer festival with a guy.
It seems like she's having trouble
deciding whether to wear one that day...
Thank you very much.
Then, that was...
All...
Um! If it's all right with you, would
you like to go out some time?
Huh?
I-It's my younger sister's
birthday... In August!
You seem like you'd be good at
picking out presents, Yoi-san.
So if it's possible, I was wondering...
I'm not sure if I'd be good
at it, but all right.
I'll think about it.
Yoi!
Coming! Later.
I know that. But...
Why did I say that?
Traveling with upperclassmen
is exciting, don't you think?
Y-Yeah.
But I can't help but notice that you're
not wearing the clothes we bought!
You're not wearing the earrings either.
I couldn't fit everything
while I was packing...
Jeez, that's just what I'm talking about.
I actually did bring them, but...
I'm still sort of
embarrassed to wear them...
Hey!
We keep you waiting?
Oh, hey.
Stare.
Stare
Huh?
Wh-What is it?!
I've never seen you
in casual clothes before.
What?
Oh, that's right.
It's a new side of you.
It's always your work clothes
or school uniform.
What?!
Oh, Um...
Stop.
You're forbidden from looking any further.
There he goes! Stupid lovebirds!
Shut up, and keep your eyes off.
Let's just go ahead and buy our tickets.
Jeez, can't even let
my guard down for a sec.
Um, that's really enough now.
Hmm? What is?
Shoulder. My shoulder.
Aw, I figured we could stay like this...
Yeah, just kiddin'!
Oh man...
Who can't let their guard down for a sec?
Oh, forgot one more thing.
You look real cute.
Hey, wait a sec on choosing seats!
Of course, we're going with reserved seating.
Y-You...
Womanizer!
Yoi on trip
Earring
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis